Business and Professional Women's Club of New York State, Inc.; Records apap117
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Photographs, 1980-1990; 5; 0.17 cubic ft.
  - National Convention, Photographs and Negatives, 1989 (Box 6 (5-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - National Convention, 1990 (Box 6 (5-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Parade of Albany Chapter, Photographs and Contact Sheets, 1986 (Box 6 (5-Photographs), Folder 11)